[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McAuliffe"]}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "I mean that is undeniably true, wasn't it Frank, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Well, McAuliffe's long history in government I'm not sure what he's talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "I mean he's right, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "He is right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Should we care, Frank Rich?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "What can I say...", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Frank Rich?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Are they anywhere near as judgmental as their parents, and grandparents may be are about this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "That's a good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "If that was a one off as he claims, do we really need to get so exercised about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "ICH: Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What do you think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "I think there's a big difference as you mentioned earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "But is he actually sensible, should he take a back step and get some treatment maybe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I think the problem is that this is what he's saying now, but he's been lying for a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "You know there's an allegation that you left this voice mails on Jonathan Martin's voicemail, what do you have to say about those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "No comment right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jonathan Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "I mean, from looking at what the quarterback said, he said that you'd asked a week ago, Jonathan Martin and Mr. Incognito would have been best pals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Yes I think that I want to say it's a mountain made out of a mole hill.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jonathan Martin", "Mr. Incognito"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Should he just choose another sport and get out of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "You have to treat it like a workplace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "I mean, eventually, you're new to the sport in some of the Americans love, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "ENEFFEE: Right, you know, it's not just about the physical party.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "If you were in the NFL tomorrow, who do you think you'd rather go to war with in a football sense if you were playing the New York Giants, Richie Incognito, the big beast who destroys all in front of him or Jonathan Martin who runs home to mommy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You know, I think that's what we're going to find out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL", "New York Giants"], "PERSON": ["Richie Incognito", "Jonathan Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "How tall are you Curt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "5'11 and three quarters I'd like to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Well you've done a U-turn on nuclear energy so have you (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "So what has reassured you on those two things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well cost, you know, if we start building nuclear power plants like we build solar panels and like we build wind turbines and like we have iPhones and everything else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Well, if I say, Chernobyl or Fukushima or whatever, how do you know that there wasn't going to be more of this if we have allowed more nuclear plants?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, look I think again, you're going to look at the context.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "I sensed there for a lot of experts, Robert Kennedy, is there an inimitability about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, those are climate experts they're not people who actually are building power plants and I would say if you talk to people who are building power plants, build particularly solar power plants or wind power plants that they'll tell you a completely different story.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131106pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "If it's so prevalent and so successful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "The kind of reactors that are advocated for this film by this film are breeder reactors which actually create more plutonium and more weapons grade plutonium.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]